ALEXANDER COVI

\((236) 515-2579

Vancouver, BC

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Reliable and motivated professional with a commitment to quality and continuous improvement. Experienced in working with clients and skilled in client management, building strong relationships, and collaborating effectively. Currently advancing studies in digital marketing, fluent in English and Italian.

SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Analytical and Managerial Abilities
- ✓ Professional Discipline

- **✓** Emotional Intelligence
- Teamwork Orientation
- Continuous Improvement Mindset

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Bertani Baggiovara

Barista, Waiter, and Market Clerk | November 2023 - January 2024

- Delivered fast and courteous service, ensuring customer satisfaction.
- Worked effectively with colleagues and supervisors to maintain a positive work environment and achieve common goals.

Opocrin (Pharmaceutical Company)

harmaceutical Technician | January 2024- September 2024

- Assisted in the production and quality control of pharmaceutical products.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to optimize production efficiency and maintain highquality standards.

Formigine Rugby Club

Sports Educator | 2017 - 2024

• Successfully managed the team through challenging periods, ensuring the development and unity of each member.

EDUCATION

• Bachelor's Degree in Digital Marketing (Ongoing)

University of Modena and Reggio Emilia (UNIMORE), Italy

Software developer (Current)

ILAC International College, Vancouver, Canada

High School Diploma in Chemistry and Health Biotechnology

I.I.S. Selmi Technical Institute, Modena, Italy

Graduated: June 2020